Hey, Doctor Jill here.
I'm not seeing patients today, so I'm in my car running around trying to get all four of my kids ready for back to school.
I imagine most of you are doing the same.
Despite the fact that one started school yesterday, we just weren't ready, but I'm going to get him ready today.
I'm reaching out because as we're starting school, I'm thinking about how we re-enter from our more relaxed summer schedule and habits.
We had the summer of our dreams, but it's time to get back to work. Work hard, play hard.
We have played hard. It's time to work hard.
I'm thinking about healthier snacks.
I'm thinking about drinking all the right water with the electrolytes.
I'm thinking about positive energy, and how we can embrace this year with goals.
I'm thinking about changing air purifiers in my house, making sure the air quality is good.
I'm also thinking about bedtime and sleep.
Making sure we're going to bed in enough time to restore our bodies from these beautiful lives we're living during the day.
And that whole thing made me want to reach out to you.
If you're getting this video from me, it's because I've met you and your sweet kiddo in the last year or so, and we've talked about their sleep-disordered breathing and how they may not be getting the rest they deserve.
So I'm reaching out. Let's touch base again.
How's it going?
I've attached to this email a sleep-disordered breathing questionnaire.
Fill it out. Let's see how your kiddo's doing.
If you want to talk about it, or bring him in for another reevaluation, let me know and we'll get you scheduled in office.
If it's not the right time, we're here for you when you're ready.
If it is the right time, give us a call.
Let's add this into your back-to-school habits.
Let's get these kids sleeping well, breathing right, and growing the way they're supposed to.
I hope everybody has a great school year, and if I don't see you in the office, I'm probably in my car driving carpool with these kids all over town.
Thanks. Talk to you soon.